{
    "questions": [
        {
            "answer": "d",
            "options": [
                "River",
                "Cave",
                "Island",
                "Aquarium"
            ],
            "question": "Where can you see different kinds of sea creatures?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "b",
            "options": [
                "Go camping",
                "Join a music club",
                "Visit an eco-farm",
                "Practise swimming"
            ],
            "question": "What activity helps students improve their musical skills?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "c",
            "options": [
                "Waterfall",
                "Cave",
                "Island",
                "River"
            ],
            "question": "Which place is usually surrounded by water?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "c",
            "options": [
                "Take lessons",
                "Grow vegetables",
                "Sleep in a tent",
                "Practise swimming"
            ],
            "question": "What do people usually do when they go camping?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "a",
            "options": [
                "Cave",
                "Waterfall",
                "Island",
                "Aquarium"
            ],
            "question": "What do people visit when they want to explore underground rock formations?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "river",
            "question": "People love to travel to the ... to enjoy the fresh air and see beautiful waterfalls.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "go camping",
            "question": "My family will ... this weekend to enjoy nature.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "practising swimming",
            "question": "She spends her free time ... because she wants to improve her skills.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "visit an eco-farm",
            "question": "We plan to ... this summer because we want to learn how to grow vegetables.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "take lessons in foreign languages",
            "question": "Many students ... to improve their speaking and writing skills.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        }
    ]
}